<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Ens on </title>
    <link>https://labs.yulrizka.com/en/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Ens on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 17:09:57 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://labs.yulrizka.com/en/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>My Desktop With i3, polybar, conky, and rofi</title>
      <link>https://labs.yulrizka.com/en/my-desktop-with-i3-polybar-conky-rofi/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 17:09:57 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://labs.yulrizka.com/en/my-desktop-with-i3-polybar-conky-rofi/</guid>
      <description>This weekend i&amp;rsquo;ve been playing with my i3 desktop settings. Here are the result 

Made with:
 Window Manager: i3 Background: Ori Color Scheme: Nord Polybar: adi1090x/polybar-themes-8 Conky: conky  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Convert Intellij Live Template to vscode Snippet</title>
      <link>https://labs.yulrizka.com/en/convert-intellij-live-template-to-vscode/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 May 2020 19:31:50 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://labs.yulrizka.com/en/convert-intellij-live-template-to-vscode/</guid>
      <description>If you are in the need of converting your custom intellij live tempate, you can use this method to transform it.
Locate the template file The first thing you need to is is to locate the template file. You can find it inside the intellij settings directory which is vary per operating system. See this documentation to locate it.
For example for my golang templte in linux, I find it under</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why for-range behaves differently depending on the size of the element (A peek into go compiler optimization)</title>
      <link>https://labs.yulrizka.com/en/why-for-range-behave-differently-depending-on-the-size-of-the-element/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Apr 2020 15:47:49 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://labs.yulrizka.com/en/why-for-range-behave-differently-depending-on-the-size-of-the-element/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s all started when my colleague asked this question.
1 2 3 4 5 6 7 8 9 10 11 12 13 14 15 16 17 18 19 20 21 22 23 24 25 26 27 28 29 30 31 32 33 34 35 36 37 38 39  package main import &amp;#34;testing&amp;#34; const size = 1000000 type SomeStruct struct { ID0 int64 ID1 int64 ID2 int64 ID3 int64 ID4 int64 ID5 int64 ID6 int64 ID7 int64 ID8 int64 } func BenchmarkForVar(b *testing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Testing go 1.5 cross compilation on raspberry pi</title>
      <link>https://labs.yulrizka.com/en/testing-go-1-dot-5-cross-compilation/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Aug 2015 17:28:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://labs.yulrizka.com/en/testing-go-1-dot-5-cross-compilation/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m so excited with the new release of golang. One particular feature is now very easy to build for multiple architecture. If you seen my other posts, I also like to tinker with my raspberry-pi. On my previous project I use either ruby or python for building some stuff. One annoying thing is dependency, setup and compilation is usually quite slow. Would be cool if I could just create some stuff in desktop and just scp the binary to pi and everything should work!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>osx-push-to-talk App</title>
      <link>https://labs.yulrizka.com/en/osx-push-to-talk-app/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Mar 2015 00:26:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://labs.yulrizka.com/en/osx-push-to-talk-app/</guid>
      <description>Push To Talk app for OSX
PushToTalk App installer   As a part of scrum teams, every day I need to give updates to my team via Google Hangout. We have a team here in the Netherlands and also in Indonesia. Some times I am in the same room as a colleague of mine. This sometimes quite annoying because I can hear my self (with a delay) from his mic.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tracking origin of bugs with git bisect</title>
      <link>https://labs.yulrizka.com/en/tracking-origin-of-bugs-with-git-bisect/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2015 23:35:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://labs.yulrizka.com/en/tracking-origin-of-bugs-with-git-bisect/</guid>
      <description>Disect the rocket, image by ProudloveNathan Proudlove  I&amp;rsquo;ve been involved with a iOS project this past week. I&amp;rsquo;m adding functionalities to the CommonSense iOS library. One of the most annoying thing is that it took about 2 minute to load the project. This is only happened in the unstable branch. The master branch seems to be working fine. So I knew that somewhere there is a commit when this starts happening.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stubbing Time.Now() in golang</title>
      <link>https://labs.yulrizka.com/en/stubbing-time-dot-now-in-golang/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2014 16:42:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://labs.yulrizka.com/en/stubbing-time-dot-now-in-golang/</guid>
      <description>Sometimes it&amp;rsquo;s really hard to test functionality that involve with system time. Especially when we want to test the function with a specific time. For example testing whether today is end of month or test 2 different behavior at a different time
Below we look into different ways we can mock or stub the time. Each with it&amp;rsquo;s own advantages and disadvantages.
Passing the time instance 1 2 3 4 5 6 7 8 9 10 11 12  func CheckEndOfMonth(now time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My account just got hacked by Romanian (Possibly)</title>
      <link>https://labs.yulrizka.com/en/my-account-just-got-hacked-by-romanian-possibly/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Jul 2013 11:58:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://labs.yulrizka.com/en/my-account-just-got-hacked-by-romanian-possibly/</guid>
      <description>You are probably familiar with above images. Some random friend sent you an email which you can instantly recognize as a spam because it only contains one link. Couple days ago I receive this email which is not the first time for me. But this time it was different. It actually came from my own Yahoo! account which I never use since more that one year ago.
My first instinct is to check whether the mail really got sent from my account or it just spoofing my email address.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>berks upload core dump</title>
      <link>https://labs.yulrizka.com/en/berks-upload-ruby-core-dump/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2013 23:26:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://labs.yulrizka.com/en/berks-upload-ruby-core-dump/</guid>
      <description>Berksfhel is cookbook dependency for chef. If you are familiar with ruby / python, think of it as a Bundler or virtual environment for chef
I faced this core dump error while doing berks upload. That command will actualy push some cookbook to a chef server.
1 2 3 4 5 6 7 8 9 10 11 12 13 14 15  $ berks upload /home/user/.rbenv/versions/1.9.3-p362/lib/ruby/gems/1.9.1/gems/celluloid-0.14.1/lib/celluloid/tasks.rb:47: [BUG] Segmentation fault ruby 1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Safely sharing credentials with PGP</title>
      <link>https://labs.yulrizka.com/en/safely-sharing-credentials-with-pgp/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2013 16:24:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://labs.yulrizka.com/en/safely-sharing-credentials-with-pgp/</guid>
      <description>When working in teams, we are sometimes required to share some password / keys with our team. The most common way for me is probably through email or some chat client. But even though its convenience it&amp;rsquo;s not actually a secure and a good practice. Especially if you are providing a service that deal with sensitive information.
Some simple approach would we communicating the password directly with a person through secure medium.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Homeward light indicator with RaspberryPi and CommonSense</title>
      <link>https://labs.yulrizka.com/en/homeward-light-indicator-with-raspberrypi-and-commonsense/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2013 20:33:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://labs.yulrizka.com/en/homeward-light-indicator-with-raspberrypi-and-commonsense/</guid>
      <description>I&#39;ve been tinkering with my [raspberry-pi][raspberry-pi] for quite some time now. What I like about it because it is cheap ($25), it&#39;s run Linux (especially debian based) and most of all it&#39;s have General Purpose Input Output pin. Since I was a kid, I always wanted to control electronic appliance remotely. Luckily my friend [@pimnijdam][pimnijdam] thought me how to control a relay board. Basically it&#39;s just like an electric switch that connect/disconnect current when you supply a low voltage.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Responsive Design</title>
      <link>https://labs.yulrizka.com/en/responsive-design/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Feb 2012 01:48:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://labs.yulrizka.com/en/responsive-design/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve been playing around with twitter bootstrap. It&amp;rsquo;s like a css framework to help designer or developer create a nice and clean site. It&amp;rsquo;s offer grid system, predefine layout, button, javascript, carousel etc. You can build website in just a few hours. Very nice for prototyping.
I&amp;rsquo;ve been using it to build this blog since it was version 1. Recently i had a chance to upgrade it to version 2. The new version offer a lot of functionalities, one the feature that I play a lot is the responsive design.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jekyll error utf-8 caracter</title>
      <link>https://labs.yulrizka.com/en/jekyll-error-utf-8-caracter/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Jan 2012 17:32:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://labs.yulrizka.com/en/jekyll-error-utf-8-caracter/</guid>
      <description>If you having a problem in jekyll when it didn&amp;rsquo;t generate a post and there is no error in the log file. you might want to check the content if there is any UTF-8 character encoding such as this ±
The problem arise if you use ruby 1.9. It rejecting a file that contain non-ASCII character. it actually got invalid multibyte char (US-ASCII) error message
to solve this. I added this line to .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Testing ruby code with benchmark_suite</title>
      <link>https://labs.yulrizka.com/en/testing-ruby-code-with-benchmark-suite/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Jan 2012 12:05:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://labs.yulrizka.com/en/testing-ruby-code-with-benchmark-suite/</guid>
      <description>Just a couple days ago I found out therubygame.com which challenge us to solve a problem with ruby. The result were measured by the fastest, slowest, shortest, longest, cheaters (yup there are also some rule).
And also I was listening to an episode of ruby rouge on Benchmarking. And there is one tools called benchmark_suite.
So there is this challenge to capitalize first letter of every word. I want to compare my code to the fastest solution there.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
